let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Oil, natural gas and coal are examples of...",
        answer: "Fossil fuels",
        options: [
        "Renewable resources",
        "Geothermal resources",
        "Fossil fuels",
        "Biofuels"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
        "Hyper Text Preprocessor",
        "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
        "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How did the dinosaurs die out?",
        answer: "An asteroid impact",
        options: [
        "DANG IT! They didn't die. In fact they excreted on your car last Friday.",
        "An asteroid impact",
        "Because of the Ice age",
        "A FLOOD 500 years ago"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What kind of small objects composes much of the universe?",
        answer: "Atoms",
        options: [
        "Atoms",
        "Dark matter",
        "Monster energy",
        "Anti-matter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What's the shape of the Earth?",
        answer: "Spheroid",
        options: [
        "Round",
        "Flat",
        "Has no shape",
        "Spheroid"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: 'Do South America and Africa fit together like a jigsaw puzzle?',
        answer: 'Yes, they do!',
        options: [
            'UNICORNS DID IT 5000 YEARS AGO',
            'Yes, they do!',
            'HECK NO!',
            'WORM KING DID IT'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: 'Which science process skill involves using your five senses to describe what is seen, heard, felt, smelt, and tasted?',
        answer: 'Observing',
        options: [
            'Observing',
            'Predicting',
            'Inferring',
            'Measuring'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: 'Which science process skill is an explanation of observations?',
        answer: 'Inferring',
        options: [
            'Observing',
            'Predicting',
            'Inferring',
            'Measuring'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: 'Which science process skill uses numbers to describe an object?',
        answer: 'Measuring',
        options: [
            'Observing',
            'Predicting',
            'Inferring',
            'Measuring'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which science process skill involves making up categories or grouping things together?",
        answer: "Classifying",
        options: [
            'Observing',
            'Classifying',
            'Inferring',
            'Measuring'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which science process skill uses a test under controlled conditions?",
        answer: "Experimenting",
        options: [
            'Observing',
            'Experimenting',
            'Inferring',
            'Measuring'
        ]
    }
];